{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196386485","data":{"timestamp":" 948196386485"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_145253"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196397968","data":{"timestamp":" 948196397968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_145253"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196441761","data":{"timestamp":" 948196441761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_145253"," gameId":" 4e123db3-c221-4344-b9a8-b8976369cfe6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__hupa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196451382","data":{"timestamp":" 948196451382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_145253"," gameId":" 4e123db3-c221-4344-b9a8-b8976369cfe6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__vuto"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196459610","data":{"timestamp":" 948196459609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_145253"," gameId":" 4e123db3-c221-4344-b9a8-b8976369cfe6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__vuto"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196469860","data":{"timestamp":" 948196469860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_145253"," gameId":" 4e123db3-c221-4344-b9a8-b8976369cfe6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__yigu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196479504","data":{"timestamp":" 948196479504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_145253"," gameId":" 4e123db3-c221-4344-b9a8-b8976369cfe6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ije"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196495781","data":{"timestamp":" 948196495781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_145253"," gameId":" 4e123db3-c221-4344-b9a8-b8976369cfe6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__unde"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196521025","data":{"timestamp":" 948196521024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_145253"," gameId":" 4e123db3-c221-4344-b9a8-b8976369cfe6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__unde"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196529444","data":{"timestamp":" 948196529444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_145253"," gameId":" 4e123db3-c221-4344-b9a8-b8976369cfe6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__unde"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196540248","data":{"timestamp":" 948196540248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_145253"," gameId":" 4e123db3-c221-4344-b9a8-b8976369cfe6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write__unde"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196558527","data":{"timestamp":" 948196558527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_145253"," gameId":" 4e123db3-c221-4344-b9a8-b8976369cfe6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write__unde"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196578167","data":{"timestamp":" 948196578167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_145253"," gameId":" 53310919-33cd-411e-a262-f3ac447ddd1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196625932","data":{"timestamp":" 948196625932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_145253"," gameId":" 53310919-33cd-411e-a262-f3ac447ddd1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196626030","data":{"timestamp":" 948196626030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_145253"," gameId":" 53310919-33cd-411e-a262-f3ac447ddd1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196634302","data":{"timestamp":" 948196634302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_145253"," gameId":" aa1a5b59-39f9-4943-ba09-adeb44582dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196673054","data":{"timestamp":" 948196673053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_145253"," gameId":" aa1a5b59-39f9-4943-ba09-adeb44582dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196673207","data":{"timestamp":" 948196673207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_145253"," gameId":" aa1a5b59-39f9-4943-ba09-adeb44582dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"end":"end"}]}